Riley Johnson Programmer

Email Riley.Johnson@trojans.dsu.edu

Phone 701-318-6330

Address 820 Washington Ave N, Madison, SD

Website therileyjohnson.com GitHub github.com/the-rileyj

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/riley-johnson-84297213a/

Professional Summary

Efficient developer with +2 years of experience in both desktop and front-end/back-end web development. Great working in teams, though capable of excelling individually. Striving to harness communication, programming, and agile learning skills in a software development role.

Experience

9/2017 – Present AWS Student Developer

Dakota State University Information Assurance Labs

- Back-end Web Development
- Front-end Web Development
- Server automation and maintenance
- Working with Amazon Web Services products

6/2017 – 8/2017 Software Quality Assurance Engineering Intern

OmniByte

- Writing automated testing solutions
- Supplying scrupulous manual testing abilities
- Composing testing procedures and plans
- Programming assistance for developers

8/2016 - 12/2016

Student Intern

OmniByte

- Automating wasteful tasks
- Providing detailed manual testing skills
- Programming assistance for developers

Education

8/2017 - Present

Dakota State University, Undergraduate, Majoring in Computer Science, Minoring in Cyber Operations and Center of Excellence in Computer Information Systems

Skills

<u>Technical</u>	<u>Programming</u>		
AWS Experience	Java	HTML	VB.NET
Computer Assembly	JavaScript	CSS	Batch Scripting
Networking	Go	Python 2/3	Bash Shell Scripting
Linux	C++	С	
Microsoft Windows	SQL	PHP	
Microsoft Office	C#	Typescript	